commodityonline.com 2018-12-31

# Commodity Online

Tranzmedia Netvision Pvt Ltd (Tranzmedia) that publishes commodityonline.com respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by Tranzmedia. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Tranzmedia, you agree to the collection and use of your data by Tranzmedia in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. 

The Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by Tranzmedia or to the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by Tranzmedia. 

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from: 

web server cookie stored on your hard drive

an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use

the domain server through which you access our service

the type of computer you're using

the type of web browser you're using

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

name including first and last name

mobile phone number and contact details

demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned);

preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on);

financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and

opinions of features on our websites.

We may also collect the following information: 

about the pages you visit/access

the links you click on our site

the number of times you access the page You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site. 

We collect the personally identifiable information from you when you register with us. During registration you are required to give us your contact information (such as name, email address, date of birth, gender, address, pin code, cell number, occupation and interests). Upon registration users may receive communications from commodityonline.com (e.g. newsletters, Mobile messages, updates) 

We use this information to contact you about the services you are using on our site and services in which you have expressed interest. 

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as occupation, education and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date, CVV verification, Name on card, billing address etc.).  We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser. 

The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which we do not own, manage or control. 

We make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone. 

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

We are the sole owners of your information collected by us at several different points on our Website. 

We use your email address to send you: 

Password reminder and registration confirmation

Changes in the service's policy or terms of use

Event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc.

Note: We send users newsletters and updates upon registration. We send newsletters and/or promotional emails on behalf of our alliance partners. 

We use your personal information to: 

help us provide personalized features

tailor our sites to your interest

to get in touch with you in the case of password retrieval and policy changes

to provide the services requested by you

to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy

We use contact information internally to: 

direct our efforts for product improvement

contact you as a survey respondent

notify you if you win any contest; and

send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to: 

remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective;

recognize your access privileges to our Web sites

track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings

make sure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly

help diagnose problems with our server

track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites

We will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you.  We do not share or rent your email addresses with third parties except our agents and alliance partners. 

We use the services of our enabling partners such as outside shipping companies, resellers, business associates to fulfill orders, and credit card processing companies to process the payment for goods and services ordered from Livingfaith.in website. These entities do not retain, store, share or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

The security of your personal information and email address is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by commodityonline.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. We do use cookies on point of collection pages of email address but we do not use them in emails. 

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

If we decide to make changes in our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to change our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us at [info@commodityonline.com]()
